EF字幕組
獵人
第一季 第3集
獵人 前情提要
Previously on Hunters...
那則音頻信息中說會發生流血事件 現在的確發生了
That audio message said blood would be spilt, and it has been.
那個帶走艾比的混球
The bastard who took Abby.
只要我們找到他 就能找到你妻子
We find out where he is, we find your wife.
我老婆怎麼會是你們中的一員呢
My wife is not one of you.
現在想看艾比嗎 來吧
You wanna see Abby now? Come on.
我們在倉庫裏的屍體上採集了一些證物
We got some forensics off the body in the warehouse.
發現受害者體內有海洛因
Turns out there was heroin in the victim's system.
不是艾比
It's not Abby.
我們無處不在 我們所向披靡
We're everywhere, and you can't stop us.
是斯拉維奇的妻子
Slavich's wife.
我把那女人撕成碎片
I tore that woman to shreds,
就像野獸一樣 我還喜歡那種感覺
like an animal... and I liked it.
裏根特工就像眼鏡蛇一樣蛻皮
Agent Regan is shedding like a freakin' cobra.
斯拉維奇跟我說的最後一句話就是我們組裏有內鬼
Slavich's last words to me were about Hunters being inside the ETU.
裏根很困惑
Regan's confused.
他覺得她是他們中的一員
He think she's one of them.
她最好小心
She better watch herself.
塞克萊頓市 西弗吉尼亞州 1997
- 嘿  - 怎麼了 艾莉森
- Hey! - What is it, Allison?
你能不能別玩這個
Could you play something else?
你在逗我嗎
Are you serious?
噪音刺得我頭疼
The noise hurts my head.
你這人真奇怪
You are so weird.
艾莉森
Allison?
發生什麼了
What happened?
你做了什麼
What'd you do?
這是意外 爸爸
It was an accident, Daddy.
- 哦 我的天哪  - 對 對不起
- Oh, my God. - I'm... I'm sorry!
- 她沒事的  - 泰德 發生什麼事了嗎
- She's okay. - Ted, everything all right out there?
我們需要幫助 快報警
We need help! Call 911!
打電話報警  他們需要幫助
Call 911! They need some help!
獵人
我們在麥卡錫倉庫內找到的癮君子屍體內
The junkie body we found in McCarthy's warehouse
有哥倫比亞·奧爾維多的海洛因
had Columbian Olvidos' heroin in her system.
翻譯 ICE  ZH
美國緝毒局去年拍到麥卡錫和五胞胎還有奧爾維多在一起的照片
DEA got pictures of McCarthy and the Quins with the Olvidos last year.
翻譯 oo  Ginny
校對/後期 Ginny
他們對自己面臨的事情完全不瞭解
They had no idea who or what they were dealing with.
五胞胎  是我在倉庫見到的那些怪胎
Quins? Those are the freaks I saw at the farmhouse.
對 這是我們起的名字
That's what we're calling 'em.
發生了什麼
What's happening?
這些照片是在通往
This picture was taken on a road
壓制  獵魔人
哥倫比亞叢林深處一製毒窩點的路上拍的
leading to a drug compound deep in the Columbian jungle.
獵人和海洛因 還有如穆斯林聖戰者般的藏身地點
Hunters and heroin, and deep like a Mujahidin situation.
統籌  Ginny
那是籌集資金的最佳方法
Tried and true method of raising funds.
女童子軍有餅乾 恐怖分子有毒品
Girl Scouts have cookies, terrorists have dope.
裏根 你聽明白了嗎
Regan. You getting all this?
獵人在叢林裏倒手毒品
The Hunters are running drugs in the jungle,
你讓我和一個新來的人去找他們
and you're sending me a new guy to find them.
- 收到  - 算上我
- Got it. - Count me in.
卡羅爾特工有啃藥史 布裏格斯
Agent Carroll has history with narcotics, Briggs.
我不是擔心他
It's not him I'm worried about.
你難道認為我需要保護嗎
You think I need protecting?
不如問問傑西·斯拉維奇吧
Oh, let's ask Jessie Slavich.
因為有裏根特工在 你才能坐在這裏 閉上你的嘴
Agent Regan is the only reason you're still here to shoot your mouth off.
你和卡羅爾
You and Carroll.
我個人認為
My two cents...
如果我們要去叢林抓獵人的話 多一個士兵不是壞事
if we're going into the jungle to catch Hunters, another soldier couldn't hurt.
好吧 布裏格斯 算你一個
All right... Briggs, you're in.
共同合作 找到他們的大本營 搗毀它
Work together, find this camp, shut it down.
抓住任何你能找到的獵人或是同夥
Capture any Hunters or collaborators you may find.
我們之前用過幾個當地人
There are some local guys we've used before.
你們可以相信他們
You can trust them.
我來處理麥卡錫的善後工作
I'll handle the McCarthy cleanup.
就這樣
That is all.
我要拿走這些
I'm taking these.
你的全家福嗎
Family pictures?
開玩笑啦
I was kidding.
別那麼嚴肅
Lighten up.
你依然是位已婚男士吧
Thought you were still a married man?
我不會在這裏處理我的皮膚問題的
I'm not getting down to my skin in here, so...
嗯
Yeah.
關於你的皮膚
About your skin thing.
還要討論這個
We're still on that?
請便
Go on.
還有沒有其他方法
Is there any other way to, you know,
辨別某人是不是……
tell if someone is... whatever you are.
我有強烈的慾望 生理上的
I get urges, physical urges.
很難控制
They're hard to control.
你說生理是指
You mean physical like...
是的 沒錯  還有
Yes, that. And other stuff.
衝動
Impulse control.
飢餓 憤怒
Hunger, rage.
她在抱怨自己的感覺嗎
Is she blaming her feelings?
接著就得開始抱怨經前綜合征了吧
Next she'll say it was PMS.
饒了她吧
Give her a break.
江山易改本性難移
A tiger doesn't change its stripes.
我們要去的地方 將需要她發揮身上的每一個長處
Where we're going, were gonna need everything she's got in her.
塞克萊頓市 西弗吉尼亞 1997
艾莉森 你在做什麼
Allison... what are you doing?
你說過那個聲音會刺痛你的耳朵
You said that hurts your ears.
確實是這樣
It does.
親愛的
Sweetie...
你對妮可做的 不過是個意外
What happened to Nicole... was a mistake.
不 不是的
No, it wasn't.
我想讓她停下 所以就推了她
I wanted her to stop, so I pushed her.
但你並不想傷害她
But you didn't mean to hurt her.
這不是你的錯
This was not your fault.
可是賈妮和安布爾說是我的錯
Janine and Amber said it was.
她們說不想再跟我做朋友了
They told me they're not gonna be my friends anymore.
你之所以會對妮可做那樣的事是因為
The reason this happened to Nicole...
我們和一般人不太一樣
is because we're different.
你 我 你的媽媽
You... me, your mom.
我要告訴你真相
I'm gonna show you the truth.
可能會有點嚇人
And it might be scary.
希望你能足夠強大勇敢
But I need you to be strong.
現在 仔細看好了
Now, watch closely.
盡量不要轉過身
Try not to turn away.
爸爸 不要  停下 快停下
Daddy, no! Stop! Stop!
- 看著 看好了  - 爸爸 不要這樣
- Keep... keep watching. - Dad, please!
不要轉頭 艾莉森
Don't look away, Allison.
這就是我們的本來面目
This is what we are.
它在我身體裏 也在你身體裏
This is in me, and it's in you, too.
這也是你傷害妮可的原因
And it's why you hurt Nicole...
我身體裏沒有這些  沒有
That isn't inside me. It isn't.
嘿 沒事的
Hey... it's okay.
沒事的
It's okay.
我從來沒想過要傷害別人
I don't ever want to hurt anyone.
那就不要有這個念頭
Then don't.
博亞卡  哥倫比亞
只靠我們自己 永遠都找不到任何東西
We'll never find anything in here on our own.
他們會出現的 他們可是職業殺手
They'll turn up. They're hired guns.
不出現 就不會有錢
No show, no dough.
嗨
Hi.
早上好
Good morning.
我叫卡羅爾
I'm Carroll.
這是布裏格斯  裏根
This is Briggs. Regan.
傑克遜派我們來的
Jackson sent us.
你們中誰是頭兒
One of you the C.O.?
亞歷杭德羅
Alejandro.
但他們
But they...
叫我馬托
call me Mato.
歡迎來到我的叢林
Welcome to my jungle.
奧爾維多的毒品營地就在這片叢林的某處
The Olvidos' drug camp is somewhere in this part of the jungle.
如果一定要我說的話 我估計在這
I had to guess, I'd say here.
但你也不確定吧
But you don't know for sure?
那片種植園可是由冷血殺手經營的
The plantation is run by cold-blooded killers.
一定藏得嚴嚴實實
They keep it hidden.
營地周圍都佈滿陷阱和狙擊手
Guard the perimeter with traps and snipers.
而我們這裏的人都是 純爺們
And these guys... puro cabrons.
前多國部隊指揮官
Former MFC.
軍人
Military.
還有哥倫比亞革命武裝力量
That and FARC.
他們都是些
They're soldiers we grew up with
寧願拿報酬幹活也不要逍遙自在的傢伙
who decided they wanted a payday instead of freedom.
你應該感謝傑克遜和他在中情局的朋友
You can thank Jackson and his CIA friends for that.
所以守衛糖果店的都是些小孩子
So they got kids guarding the candy store.
糖果店的主人是小孩子
Kids own the candy store.
而奧爾維多家族 他們從不開玩笑
The Olvidos, they don't play.
要是你偷東西的話 他們會把你眼睛挖出來
They cut your eyes out for stealing.
但如果是你的話
But you...
他們可能會索取點別的
但從沒有人能闖入那個營地
But no one has ever made it to that camp uninvited.
軍隊 緝毒局 都不曾有過
Not the army, not your DEA... no one.
你們確定要這麼做嗎
You're sure you want to do this?
怎麼 你害怕了
Why, you getting cold feet?
我
Me?
沒有 我只想確定 大難臨頭之時
No... I just want to be sure you won't run away
你會不會轉身就逃
when the fan hits the shit.
你還是擔心自己吧
You worry about your own.
我們絕不會當縮頭烏龜
We're sure as hell not backing down.
馬托說製毒營地就在十英里開外的地方
Mato says the drug camp is ten miles in.
他傍晚前會把我們帶到那裏
He'll get us there by nightfall.
對於一個在坎大哈（阿富汗城市）執行過任務的人來說 這都不算什麼吧
Not bad for a guy who did his tours of duty in Kandahar.
我寧可去阿富汗 也不願意來這種滿是蕨類植物的山溝
I'd take Afghanistan over this FernGully shit any day.
我也討厭綠乎乎的東西
Yeah, I hate this green stuff, too.
你不是吃素麼  這些在你眼裏 不就跟沙拉一樣麼
You're a vegetarian. Isn't this all just... salad?
我現在是跟著朵拉(卡通片人物）去探險麼
Now I'm being led by Dora the Explorer.
態度放尊重點
Best keep that attitude to yourself.
我們必須謹慎
We need it.
尤其獵人就在附近之時
Especially if there are Hunters out there.
奧爾維多的歡迎方式
An Olvidos welcome.
女士優先
Ladies first.
你聽見什麼動靜了嗎
You hearing anything?
放下武器  等一下  放下武器
Drop the weapon now! Hold on! Drop!
馬托
Mato!
- 不要開火  - 等等
- Hold fire! - Wait!
不要開火
Hold fire!
是工人
Workers.
有武器
Armed.
足以殺掉我們所有人
They could have killed us all.
放下武器
Drop the weapon.
我不會傷害你的
I'm not gonna hurt you.
別害怕 你現在已經安全了
Don't worry, now you're safe.
我不會傷害你的
I'm not gonna hurt you.
你現在沒事了
You're okay now.
你安全了
You're safe.
他們是你的家人嗎
This is your family?
對嗎
This?
你的家人呢
What happened with your family?
她從林子裏衝出來 帶走了我媽媽
She came out of the jungle and took my Mom.
她說了什麼
What did she say?
有人從林子裏衝出來 帶走了她媽媽
Someone came out of the jungle and took her mother.
小妹妹
Friend.
是誰
Who?
誰帶走了你媽媽
Who took your Mom?
怪物
A monster.
塞克萊頓市 西佛吉尼亞州 2005年
艾莉森
Allison!
艾莉森 開門
Allison, open the door!
你在幹嘛  你瘋了嗎
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
- 不就是大麻麼  - 你現在必須離開這兒
- It's just weed. - You need to leave, now.
啊 天啊
Oh, my God!
剛剛那是地震嗎  出什麼事了
Was that an earthquake? What's happening?
我跟你說過的那些人 那些不可信的人
The people I told you about, the ones we can't trust.
他們在這裏  來吧 快點
They're here. Come on, hurry.
我的耳朵
My ears!
媽媽
Mom!
爸爸 我好害怕
Dad, I'm scared.
出什麼事了
What's happening?
拿著這個  爬上阿勒格尼山
Take this. Climb Allegheny.
跟著你的直覺走
Follow your instincts.
我脫身後會去找你的
I'll come get you when I can.
但我不能就這麼走了  媽媽怎麼辦
But I can't just leave. What about Mom?
艾莉森 聽著 你要勇敢
Allison, listen, I need you to be my brave girl.
好嗎  跟直覺走就好了
Okay? Just follow your instincts.
你會沒事的
You'll be fine.
趕緊從窗戶出去  現在  馬上
Now out the window. Now. Go, now!
她說一隻怪物帶走了她的母親
She says a monster took her mother.
怪物  什麼樣的
A monster? How it was?
什麼樣的
How it was?
再問問她
Ask her again.
我們需要弄清楚她到底看到了什麼
We need to know exactly what she saw.
是拉莫哈娜
It's La Mojana.
當地傳說裏的人物
It's a local legend.
一個可以改變外形的女人
A woman that changes shape,
引誘人進叢林 然後吃了他們
takes people into the jungle and eats them.
毒梟宣傳這個傳說以阻止農民進入叢林
The cartel encourages it to keep peasants out of the jungle.
是莫哈娜嗎
It was the Mojana?
帶走你媽媽的那個人
That took your Mom?
是的  拉莫哈娜
Yes. La Mojana.
拉莫哈娜
La Mojana.
我們得把她帶回她的營地
We need to get her back to the camp.
不不不  她就待在這裏
No, no, no... she stays.
前方險阻未知
We're walking into a shit storm,
我需要人手 抓一個是一個
and I need every soldier I got.
她還是個孩子
She's just a kid.
我要把她帶回去
I'm taking her back.
你有任務
You got a job to do...
和我們一起
with us.
弗林說得沒錯
Flynn's right.
哦  出現了個拉莫哈娜
Oh... we got La Mojana out there,
你就突然離不開我咯
and suddenly you need me.
唷 芭比大兵 她是個大姑娘啦
Yo, G.I. Joe Barbie, she's a big girl.
我在她那麼大的時候 都手撕好幾人了
I was slitting throats when I was her age.
你想拿到之前傑克遜答應的薪水嗎
You want your payday like Jackson promised?
讓你最弱的手下帶這姑娘回營地
Send your weakest man to take the girl back to camp,
不然的話 我們來帶
otherwise, we take her.
你就什麼也撈不著
And you go home empty-handed.
你做決定吧 頭兒
Choice is yours, jefe.
卡洛斯
Carlos.
卡洛斯 把這女孩兒帶回營地
謝謝
Thanks.
不客氣
You're welcome.
走吧
Let's go.
什麼時候告訴他 我們是在打怪物 而不是對抗毒梟
When do we tell him we're fighting monsters and not a drug cartel?
什麼也不用說
We don't tell them anything.
而且他們也不是怪物
And they're not monsters.
他們只是非人類罷了
They're just not human.
阿勒格尼山脈 西弗吉尼亞州 2005
如果你在讀這個的話 說明我已經不在你身邊了
If you're reading this, it means I'm no longer with you.
你現在起得靠自己了 你要堅強
You're on your own now, and you have to be strong.
無論你做什麼 我都是你的父親
No matter what you do, I am your father,
你是我的小心肝
and you're my little girl.
我會永遠愛你
And I will always love you.
看看這邊
Check it out.
一直向前
Straight ahead.
我覺得我們找到營地了
I think we found our camp.
看來沒人啊
Looks empty.
沒有看守 什麼都沒有
No guards, nothing.
廢墟
Ghost town.
裏根
Regan?
我聽不到動靜
I don't hear a thing.
我們從下面過去吧
Let's move in from below.
安全
Clear.
空無一人  外面的屍體一定是工人
Empty. The bodies outside must be the workers.
- 大屠殺  - 安全
- A massacre. - Clear.
沒有槍傷
No bullet wounds.
沒有槍戰的痕跡  只有
No signs of firefight. Just...
被分屍的屍體
Ripped apart.
到底是誰這麼心狠手辣
What the hell could have done this?
弗林
Flynn?
你發現了什麼
What did you find?
腳印
Footprints.
看起來是不久前的
They look fresh.
閉嘴 這是我的問題
Shut up, it's my problem.
嘿 嗯 我們搜索了整個營地
Hey... yeah, we searched the entire camp.
無人生還
There's no one left here alive.
也沒發現什麼
Nothing more to see.
不 還不能走
No, we're not leaving.
我們現在返程 還能在天黑前回去
We go now, we might make it back before dark.
哦 他們要睡覺了嗎
Oh, is it past their bedtime?
是的 是的
Yeah... yeah.
因為我們已經完成了任務 把你們帶到營地
'Cause we did our job... got you to the camp.
這是我答應傑克遜的
That's what I told Jackson we'd do,
已經完成了
and it's done.
這是你的林地嗎
Is this your jungle?
是的
Yes.
那就拿出你該有的樣子
Then act like it.
你們不是為緝毒行動來的
You're not here for a drug bust.
布裏格斯 我們一起守夜吧
Briggs... let's set up a watch.
輪流守 一直到明天早上
We'll take shifts till morning.
馬托 你和你的部下
Mato... you and your men
可以清理下外面的屍體
can clean up the bodies outside.
我們去搜查製毒室
We'll search the lab.
他們在生產海洛因
They were producing heroin.
看看這
Look at this.
看這個
Check this out.
這具屍體和外面的不同
That body wasn't killed like the ones outside.
傷口和麥卡錫倉庫裏的
It's the same wounds as the junkie
癮君子一樣
in McCarthy's warehouse.
我搗毀過很多製毒窩點
I've raided dozens of drug labs,
從沒見過這樣的
I've never seen anything like this.
此事另有隱情
Something else was going on.
還是暖的
It's still warm.
他們在破壞證據
They were destroying evidence.
和人
And people.
計劃周全 毫無破綻
No loose ends.
他們好像一直先我們一步
Like they were one step ahead of us.
斯拉維奇跟我說 我們有內鬼
Slavich told me they had someone on the inside.
內鬼  不可能吧
A mole? That's crazy.
那是什麼
What is that?
嗯 是外皮
Yeah, it's skin.
嗯
Yeah.
某種身體組織 不是人類的
It's some kind of tissue, not human.
他們到底在這兒幹嘛
What the hell were they doing here?
去掉痛苦
Taking the pain away.
芝加哥 伊利諾斯州 2012
還想拿獎賞麼
You want a medal?
我交班時間快到了  滾邊兒
My break's almost over. Shoo.
瘋婊子
Crazy fucking bitch.
我會打電話給你的
I'll call you!
才怪
Not.
嘿
Hey.
在幹什麼
What are you doin'?
關你屁事 臭傻逼
None of your business, dick wad.
你說啥
What did you say?
你聽到的  蠢驢
You heard me, donut ass.
面對牆站好
Up against the wall.
放了他
Let him go!
放了他 不然我開槍了
Let him go, or I'll shoot!
聽見什麼沒  在外面嗎
Hear anything? Is it out there?
我不知道  可能吧
I don't know. Could be.
天沒亮 什麼也幹不了
Can't do much till morning.
至少第一個被五馬分屍的會是布裏格斯
At least Briggs will be the first one getting ripped apart.
什麼
What?
他沒讓你這個獵人好過吧 處處針對你
After all the shit he gives you for being a Hunter?
布裏格斯恨我是有原因的
Briggs has his reasons for hating me.
愛亦是
And loving me.
很複雜
It's complicated.
你們倆
Did you two...?
不不不 天
No. No. God, no.
我不是他的菜
I'm not his type.
而且 他喜歡獨來獨往
Besides, he's kind of a loner,
我怕你還沒看出來
in case you hadn't figured that out yet.
也不能說我怪他
Can't say I blame him.
我見過一些人做出極惡之事
I've seen human beings do some heinous shit.
但我從沒見過這樣的
But I've never seen anything like that.
來點吧
This helps.
所以酒對你的影響不像
So alcohol doesn't affect you like...
不不  但我喜歡喝酒這種活動
No. No. But I like the ritual.
讓我覺得自己是正常人
It makes me feel normal.
我和你相反
It's pretty much the opposite for me.
我喜歡它讓我覺得自己沒那麼正常
I like how it makes me feel not normal.
你是不是一直看起來都那麼像
Did you always look... so...
什麼  人類
What? Human?
自打我記事起就是
As far as I can remember.
我一直以為自己是呢 直到我父母告訴我不是
Thought I was, until my parents told me I wasn't.
你的妻子 你從沒懷疑過
Your wife... you never suspected?
什麼
What?
她可能是外星人嗎
That she could be from outer space?
不
No.
我特麼為什麼要那麼想
Had no damn reason to think she might be.
但 看著你
But, watching you...
我覺得還真有可能
I'd say it's possible.
米格爾
Miguel!
米格爾 歐內斯托
Miguel, Ernesto!
回來  回來
Come back! Come back!
好運  我逃命去了
Good luck. I'll back off.
米格爾  你在哪裏
Miguel! Where are you?
你死定了 你個混蛋
You're gonna fry, you bastard.
馬托的手下全被殺死了
This killed all of Mato's men.
那是什麼鬼
What the hell is that?
它要逃走了
It's getting away.
那是什麼
What was that?
不管是什麼
Whatever it was...
反正不是人類
it wasn't human.
我的手機呢  我要叫後援
Where's my cell phone? I'm calling in backup.
如果必要 我真要叫上所有軍隊
The whole God damn army if I have to.
我們要找到那東西 然後殺了它
We will find that thing and go kill it...
能告訴我 這到底是怎麼一回事嗎
Wanna tell me what the hell that was about?
保密協議  傑克遜的命令
Containment protocol. Jackson's orders.
他看到太多了  他會說出去的
He saw too much. He was about to talk.
她說得沒錯  地外反恐行動組的規定
She's right. ETU rules.
我們不能讓別人知道這些
We can't let any of this get out.
殺死他手下的東西還在外遊蕩
Whatever killed his men is still out there.
我們必須通知傑克遜 走吧
We need to notify Jackson, get moving.
裏根 如果我沒有加入行動組
Regan, if I hadn't have joined the unit,
你也會把我處置掉嗎
would you have... contained me?
不是人類外表嗎
Not in human form?
那是披著什麼皮的怪物
Well, what form is it in?
我也不太清楚
I don't know, exactly.
我只能確定是一個獵人
All I know for sure is that it's a Hunter.
馬托也看見了嗎
And Mato saw it?
他有沒有被
Has he been...?
已經解決了
It's been handled.
你的所謂保密協議 令我們人手緊缺
Your protocol left us shorthanded.
我們需要額外支援  派空中之眼無人機過來
We need additional support. Eyes in the sky.
我盡力而為
I'll see what I can do.
我們現在就需要  等不到明天早上了
We need it now. Can't wait till the morning.
- 明白  - 那東西晚上也能行動
- Understood. - That thing can hunt at night.
它有優勢
It has the advantage.
你能定位目標對象的位置嗎
You have a location on the target?
它受傷了 而且很害怕
It's injured, scared.
我覺得它會躲到山裏去
I think it'll head to the mountains.
你覺得還是你確定
You think or you know?
反正我會這麼做
That's what I would do.
就我們對他們語言的瞭解而言 還算說得過去
That makes sense with what we understand about their language.
地勢越高
Higher elevation means more miles
越能先發制人
to anticipate potential attacks.
我們原本一個小時之內就可以派無人機過去
We could have a drone out there in an hour.
出什麼狀況了
And then what happens?
有個愛荷華州的22歲的
22-year-old kid from Iowa
斯諾登狂飯 用遊戲機控制器
with an Xbox controller and a Snowden complex
把無人機黑掉了
gets one of these things in his sights?
怎麼解決
How do we contain that?
車到山前必有路
We'll cross that bridge when we come to it.
我會聯繫蘭利
I'll reach out to Langley.
如果我們真想抓到它 現在就應該出發了
If we wanna catch this thing, we gotta leave now.
ETU曾經抓到過跟你不一樣的獵人嗎
Has ETU ever caught one that doesn't look like you?
我們從未抓到過任何形態的活口
We've never captured one alive in any form.
那麼我們這次最好能抓到一個 對吧
Then we better... catch this one, right?
天那麼黑 我們怎麼找得到它
How we gonna find it in the dark?
有志者事竟成
You can find anything if you want it badly enough.
庫克郡懲教中心 伊利諾斯州 芝加哥市 2012年
艾莉森 你好
Hello, Allison.
我叫特拉斯·傑克遜
My name is Truss Jackson.
我來自國土安全部
Homeland Security.
我不是來傷害你的
I'm not here to hurt you.
看什麼看 你個糟老頭
Stop staring, you dirty old freak.
怎麼著 以前沒見過女的
What, you never seen a girl before?
只是沒見過你這樣的
Not like you.
幾年前  我把你的
I have an... old photograph of you
一張老照片錄入系統
that I put into the system years ago,
就怕你萬一哪天被警察逮捕
just in case you ever got arrested.
就是這張
And here you are.
挺可愛
Cute kid.
但不是我
But that's not me.
艾莉森·裏根 來自西佛吉尼亞州的塞克萊頓市
Allison Regan of Circleton, West Virginia.
泰德·裏根與利安娜·裏根的女兒
Daughter of Ted and Liana Regan.
沒聽說過
Never heard of 'em.
16歲時 家裏被不明入侵者闖入 而失蹤
Disappeared age 16 after a home invasion by unidentified intruders.
你確定這不是你嗎
You sure that's not who you are?
行動
Go.
蘭利不允許
Langley said no.
- 行動終止  - 為什麼
- You have to abort. - Why?
見鬼
Bullshit!
如果沒有後援 你們不堪一擊
Without backup, you're vulnerable.
沒有無人機 你們什麼都看不見
Without a drone, you're blind.
太危險了
It's too dangerous.
它受傷了  優勢在我們這邊
It's injured. We have the advantage.
它可是獵人的新變體
It's a new form of Hunter.
行動終止
Abort.
這是命令
That's an order.
信號不好  你要我們匯報嗎
You're breaking up. You said report?
行動終止  我說終止
Abort! I said abort.
收到  我們會在完成任務後向您匯報 完畢
Copy that! We'll complete the mission and report, over.
卡羅爾
Carroll!
我們這回要倒大霉了
We're gonna catch shit for that.
最好物有所值
Well, we better make it worth it.
在樹上
In the trees!
布裏格斯
Briggs!
真特麼見鬼
You piece of shit!
- 我沒事  - 是那些毒販子設下的陷阱
- I'm okay. - A perimeter trap from the drug cartel.
用得著你說
Oh, now you tell me.
準備好了嗎  數到三
Ready? On three.
- 來吧  - 1
- Go on. - One...
喀嗒聲越來越弱了
The clicks are getting fainter.
好吧 你去追吧
All right, you go.
我來照看布裏格斯
I'll take care of Briggs.
她會被那個生物撕碎的
She could get ripped by whatever that thing is.
也可能反過來
Or she tears it up.
正好兩不耽誤 雙贏
What they call a win-win.
是啊
Right.
裏根又怎麼惹著你了
So what's your beef with Regan?
我可不像你那麼喜歡人形獵人
Oh, I don't like human Hunters like you do.
她真他媽能幹
She's been pretty damn useful.
她不是我見過的唯一一個獵人
She's not the only one I've met.
我曾經與澳洲特種部隊在阿富汗執行任務
I was with Australian Special Forces in Afghanistan.
我們還以為找到了恐怖分子的巢穴
We thought we were hitting a terrorist cell.
結果房間裏只有一個人
Turned out to be just one guy in a room.
我們兩人衝進去
Two of us went in.
火力大開
Opened fire, both clips.
那人毫髮未傷
Nothing.
然後
And then...
它撲向布蘭登
it leapt at Brendan
把他撕成了碎片
and it ripped him apart.
不慌不忙 戲弄意味十足
But slowly... playfully.
就像貓戲弄老鼠一樣
Like a cat.
整個過程中
And the whole time,
它一直盯著我
it kept looking at me.
就像那是一場表演
Like it was a show.
獵人奪走了你所愛之人
Hunters took the one you love.
我也有同樣遭遇
They did that to me, too.
你不能相信她
You can't trust her.
不管外表再怎麼純良
And whatever they look like on the surface...
它們骨子裏還是惡魔
they're monsters underneath.
伊利諾斯州 芝加哥市 2012年
你太狠了吧
You're ruthless.
世界盡在我的掌控之中
World domination cometh.
你的殺人本能是來自父母的嗎
You get the killer instinct from your parents?
我父母不是早死了麼
My parents are dead, aren't they?
其實 我們對你 你的父母
Truth is, we don't know much about anything about...
都瞭解甚少
your parents, about you, about any of it.
所以你狗屁不懂
So you don't know shit.
你不瞭解我
Not about me.
沒人瞭解我
No one does.
這麼多年來 你一直留著父親給你的信
You kept his letter from your dad for years.
每個人都需要精神支柱
Everybody needs someone.
你的父母
Your parents...
他們和你一樣
they were like you.
對嗎
Weren't they?
是
Yeah.
我們一樣
They were like me.
那你是什麼
And what are you?
我不知道
I don't know.